blackworld.com 2014-04-28

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement for Blackworld™**  
  
---|---  
  
**Blackworld™** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Blackworld™ ](http://www.blackworld.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information. 

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. We also use cookies for other purposes. 

####  Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers, and to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Order Forms 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). 

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Blackworld™** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Special Relationships 

#### As a general rule, Blackworld™ will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please refer to the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed. _Business Partners & Sponsors: _  
Blackworld™ may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. Details of shared use can be found in specific Terms of Service or Use Agreements, and sweepstakes and promotions rules. Some or all data collected during a Blackworld™ promotion may be shared with a sponsor. If personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give Blackworld™ permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your email address will be shared. If more information will be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer. 

**_Third Party Cookies & Advertisments_**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

####  Public Forums 

This site provides links to chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Children's Guidelines**

Naturally, the safety of children is very important to us. Blackworld™ recommends that parents and kids try our Kids Section, designed especially for users between the ages of 7 and 12. Sites listed on Blackworld Kids have all been prudently selected . This selection process ensures that these sites are fun and age-appropriate for our younger audience. Blackworld™ does not collect personally identifiable information from children. Blackworld™ is a general audience web site. Should any child under age 13 attempt to register with Blackworld™, we shall at this present time decline such an application until Blackworld™ fully establishes appropriate account facillities under strict parental support, guidance and approval. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. Blackworld™ does not share personal information about users under the age of 13 with third parties and we do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age. In addition, Blackworld™ will not send any direct email offers to users who indicate they are under the age of 13. 

####  Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us . 

  1. You can send email to [ info@blackworld.com ](mailto:info@blackworld.com)

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [info@blackworld.com ](mailto:info@blackworld.com)

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

* * *

Copyright 2012 Blackworld **™** All Rights Reserved
